export const questionAnswers = [
  {
    question: `What is raw honey?`,
    answer: `Direct from bee farm without any fabrication process`,
  },
  {
    question: `Why raw honey?`,
    answer: `To take 100% nutrient include “yeast” and “magnesium”. These are easy to be lost in any fabrication process`,
  },
  {
    question: `Why do people fabricate raw honey?`,
    answer: `To kill the natural yeast inside raw honey to stop the fermentation process. So then, the honey could be kept for a long time in the store.`,
  },
  {
    question: `Can we consume fermented raw honey?`,
    answer: `As long as it is not taste sour and smelly. You could consume it. Some people like the taste. It has some beer smell & taste. Thailand has honey beer, the most important process to ferment the honey`,
  },
  {
    question: `How people use raw honey?`,
    answer: `80% is for drinking purpose, others are to fabricate to other healthcare products such as garlic honey, lemon honey, ginger honey and so on`,
  },
  {
    question: `Why there is white bubble in the bottle?`,
    answer: `Shaking during delivery will cause this. They will disappear if you leave there for sometime. If it is not disappearing, that means the honey has absorbed enough water to start thier early stage fermentation. 
    `,
  },
  {
    question: `Why every batch of honey we buy from you has a different taste?`,
    answer: `Bees are harvesting different flowers each time. Although, the environment is full of the same flower. However, Bees might also flies up to 3km to harvest different flower`,
  },
  {
    question: `Why your honey out of stock so fast`,
    answer: `Raw honey is seasonal products. Same area flowers will not bloom all year long. `,
  },
  {
    question: `Does rainy season affect honey outcome?`,
    answer: `Definitely, bee will work less. Plus, the moisture level in the honey is too high. We will not sell this to you.`,
  },
  {
    question: `Does your company sell other raw honey?`,
    answer: `Yes, for pre-order only (deposit is required). We have durian flower, osmanthus flower, & pineapple flower`,
  },
  {
    question: `Could I buy a bottle of honey as a tester?`,
    answer: `Yes, we have 120g tester available.`,
  },
]
